Guide to the Class of 1958, Yale College, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Class of 1958 interviews [Videos recordings], circa 1992; Accession 1998-A-054
  - 1992 September 11-1992 September 12
    - Engel, Dick-First interview
      - Copy 4 of 4 (Box 39c)
    - Engel, Dick-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 39)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 39a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 39b)
      - Copy 4 of 4 (Box 39c)
    - Freed, Jack
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 39)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 39a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 39b)
      - Copy 4 of 4 (Box 39c)
    - Leeby, Reg
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 39)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 39a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 39b)
      - Copy 4 of 4 (Box 39c)
  - 1992 September 16-1992 September 17
    - Bullock, William
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 40)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 40a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 40b)
    - Clemens, Fred
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 40)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 40a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 40b)
    - Heffernan, George
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 40)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 40a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 40b)
    - Rathbone, Charles
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 40)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 40a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 40b)
  - 1992 September 18
    - Harter, Richard
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 41)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 41a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 41b)
    - Lytle, Bill
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 41)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 41a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 41b)
    - Smith, George
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 41)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 41a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 41b)
    - Spark, Richard
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 41)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 41a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 41b)
    - Travers, Linus
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 41)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 41a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 41b)
  - 1992 September 19-1992 September 20
    - Arnold, Peter
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 42)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 42a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 42b)
    - Cowles, Phillip
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 42)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 42a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 42b)
    - Henderson, John
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 42)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 42a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 42b)
    - McAdams, Ken
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 42)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 42a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 42b)
    - Smith, Sibley
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 42)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 42a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 42b)
  - 1992 September 23-1992 September 26
    - Gillespie, Bill
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 43)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 43a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 43b)
    - McCoy, Robert
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 43)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 43a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 43b)
    - Miller, Bart-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 43)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 43a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 43b)
    - Miller, Bart-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 43)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 43a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 43b)
    - Minear, Larry
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 43)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 43a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 43b)
    - Weymouth, Frolic-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 43)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 43a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 43b)
    - Weymouth, Frolic-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 43)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 43a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 43b)
  - 1992 September 26
    - Cantor, Fred
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 44)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 44a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 44b)
    - Ehrlich, David
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 44)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 44a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 44b)
    - Gastwirth, Joseph
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 44)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 44a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 44b)
    - Pierce, John
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 44)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 44a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 44b)
    - Sears, Joe
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 44)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 44a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 44b)
    - Wentworth, Thomas (Tom) Foote
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 44)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 44a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 44b)
  - 1992 September 27
    - Anderson, George
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 45)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 45a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 45b)
    - Meezy, Steve
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 45)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 45a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 45b)
    - O'Donovan, Charlie
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 45)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 45a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 45b)
    - Pfeffer, Richard
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 45)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 45a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 45b)
    - Rafferty, Mike
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 45)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 45a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 45b)
    - Stewart, Van
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 45)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 45a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 45b)
    - Wight, Peter
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 45)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 45a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 45b)
  - 1992 September 29
    - Bartlett, Charles J.
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 46)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 46a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 46b)
    - Bragen, Harold
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 46)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 46a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 46b)
    - Day, Charles
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 46)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 46a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 46b)
    - Ferguson, Alfred
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 46)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 46a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 46b)
    - White, Jack
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 46)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 46a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 46b)
  - 1992 September 30
    - Effenbein, Bruce
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 47)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 47a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 47b)
    - Holm, Al
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 47)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 47a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 47b)
    - Lapham, Peter
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 47)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 47a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 47b)
    - McCullough, Tony
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 47)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 47a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 47b)
    - McQuiston, Robert E.
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 47)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 47a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 47b)
    - Najarian, Clint
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 47)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 47a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 47b)
  - 1992 October 1-1992 October 3
    - Fagan, Charles
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 48)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 48a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 48b)
    - Ward, Peter
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 48)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 48a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 48b)
    - Weir, Donald
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 48)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 48a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 48b)
  - 1992 October 3
    - Darby, James
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 49)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 49a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 49b)
    - Faix, Phillip
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 49)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 49a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 49b)
    - Floyd, Ed
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 49)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 49a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 49b)
    - Marks, Ed
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 49)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 49a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 49b)
    - Sherman, Doug
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 49)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 49a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 49b)
    - Van Wormer, Ted
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 49)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 49a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 49b)
  - 1992 October 5
    - Aikenhead, Tom
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 50)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 50a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 50b)
    - Barnes, Calvin
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 50)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 50a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 50b)
    - Chairamonte, Larry
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 50)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 50a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 50b)
    - Feinstein, Steve
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 50)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 50a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 50b)
    - Morgan, Robert-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 50)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 50a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 50b)
    - Ness, Phillip
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 50)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 50a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 50b)
    - Paul, Roland
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 50)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 50a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 50b)
    - Whitcomb, Roger
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 50)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 50a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 50b)
    - Winkworth, Dave
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 50)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 50a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 50b)
  - 1992 October 5-1992 October 8
    - Jackson, Christo
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 51)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 51a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 51b)
    - Leuze, Robert
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 51)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 51a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 51b)
    - Loeb, Peter
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 51)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 51a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 51b)
    - Morgan, Robert-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 51)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 51a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 51b)
    - Porterfield, Chris
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 51)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 51a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 51b)
    - Zarem, Bobby
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 51)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 51a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 51b)
  - 1992 October 8
    - Downey, Mort
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 52)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 52a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 52b)
    - Lindskog, David-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 52)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 52a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 52b)
    - Porbert, Ted
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 52)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 52a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 52b)
    - Spelman, Hoyt
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 52)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 52a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 52b)
    - Welch, Perry
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 52)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 52a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 52b)
  - 1992 October 8-1992 October 11
    - Ascheim, Dr. Robert
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 53)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 53a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 53b)
    - Carlson, Richard
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 53)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 53a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 53b)
    - Case, Richard
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 53)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 53a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 53b)
    - Greenspan, Burton
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 53)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 53a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 53b)
    - Haller, Bob
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 53)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 53a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 53b)
    - Middlebrook, Stephen
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 53)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 53a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 53b)
    - Rifkind, Robert
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 53)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 53a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 53b)
  - 1992 October 11-1992 October 14
    - Clayman, Martin
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 54)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 54a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 54b)
    - Elliot, Ralph
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 54)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 54a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 54b)
    - Letendre, Andrew
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 54)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 54a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 54b)
    - Niles, John
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 54)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 54a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 54b)
  - 1992 October 15
    - Janeway, Harold
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 55)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 55a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 55b)
  - 1992 October 16
    - Duchin, Peter-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 2 (Box 56)
      - Copy 2 of 2 (Box 56a)
  - 1992 October 16-1992 October 19
    - Duchin, Peter-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 2 (Box 57)
      - Copy 2 of 2 (Box 57a)
    - Robinson, Don
      - Copy 1 of 2 (Box 57)
      - Copy 2 of 2 (Box 57a)
    - Wheeler, Tom
      - Copy 1 of 2 (Box 57)
      - Copy 2 of 2 (Box 57a)
  - 1992 October 20-1992 October 23
    - Burke, David
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 58a)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 58c)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 58e)
    - Lee, Roger
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 58a)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 58c)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 58e)
    - McDonald, Robert
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 58)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 58b)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 58d)
  - 1992 October 21
    - Bent, John
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 59)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 59a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 59b)
    - Bober, Art
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 59)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 59a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 59b)
    - Burgess, Van
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 59)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 59a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 59b)
    - Frank, Don
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 59)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 59a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 59b)
    - Jackson, Dick
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 59)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 59a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 59b)
    - Romas, Chris
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 59)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 59a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 59b)
  - 1992 October 22
    - Bulova, Stephen
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 60)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 60a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 60b)
    - Carroll, Win
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 60)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 60a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 60b)
    - Hoffman, Paul
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 60)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 60a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 60b)
    - Koehler, Hans
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 60)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 60a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 60b)
    - Snyder, Alvin
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 60)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 60a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 60b)
  - 1992 October 24
    - Goodyear, Rummy
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 61)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 61a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 61b)
    - Levin, Ron
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 61)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 61a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 61b)
    - Milius, Peter
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 61)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 61a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 61b)
    - Russell, Ted
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 61)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 61a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 61b)
    - Stalford, Charlie
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 61)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 61a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 61b)
  - 1992 October 26-1992 October 27
    - Riggs, John
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 62)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 62a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 62b)
    - Sullivan, Scott
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 62)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 62a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 62b)
  - 1992 October 27-1992 October 28
    - Carmody, Basil
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 63)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 63a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 63b)
    - Pilsbury, Henry
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 63)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 63a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 63b)
  - 1992 November
    - Cavallon, Mike (Box 86)
    - Kroll Jr., Fred (Box 86)
  - 1992 November 1
    - Schiavone, Joel-Interview 1A
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 64)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 64a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 64b)
    - Schiavone, Joel-Interview 2A
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 64)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 64a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 64b)
  - 1992 November 1-1992 November 3
    - Bush, George H.W.
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 65)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 65a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 65b)
    - Norton, Ed
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 65)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 65a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 65b)
    - Schiavone, Joel-Interview 1B
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 65)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 65a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 65b)
    - Schiavone, Joel-Interview 2B
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 65)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 65a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 65b)
  - 1992 November 1-1992 November 3
    - Bensky, Larry-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 66)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 66a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 66b)
    - Bensky, Larry-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 66)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 66a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 66b)
    - McConnell, Frank
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 66)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 66a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 66b)
    - Owen, Bill
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 66)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 66a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 66b)
  - 1992 November 5
    - Hogen, Tim
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 67)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 67a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 67b)
    - Hughes, Jim
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 67)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 67a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 67b)
    - Marsh, Gordon
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 67)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 67a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 67b)
    - Watrous, Phil
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 67)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 67a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 67b)
  - 1992 November 5
    - Cushman, Bob
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 68)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 68a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 68b)
    - Davis, Michael
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 68)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 68a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 68b)
    - Lamey, Ron
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 68)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 68a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 68b)
    - Stubenbord, Bill
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 68)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 68a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 68b)
  - 1992 November 5-1992 November 7
    - Bull, Sherman
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 69)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 69a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 69b)
    - Kovner, Victor
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 69)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 69a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 69b)
    - Turner, Jon
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 69)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 69a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 69b)
  - 1992 November 6
    - Hoge, Jim
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 70)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 70a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 70b)
  - 1992 November 12
    - Alderman, Myles-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 71)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 71a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 71b)
    - Daniels, Doug-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 71)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 71a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 71b)
    - Moore, Ed-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 71)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 71a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 71b)
    - Sammons, Jeff
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 71)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 71a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 71b)
    - Seeley, Bill
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 71)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 71a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 71b)
    - Watson, Peter
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 71)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 71a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 71b)
  - 1992 November 12
    - Alderman, Myles-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 72)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 72a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 72b)
    - Etkind, Ed
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 72)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 72a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 72b)
    - Hedden, John
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 72)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 72a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 72b)
    - Loughlin, Eddie
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 72)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 72a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 72b)
    - Sturges, Michael D.
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 72)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 72a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 72b)
  - 1992 November 13-1992 November 14
    - Crawford, Karl
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 73)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 73a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 73b)
  - 1992 November 14
    - Clark, Robert
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 74)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 74a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 74b)
    - Davidson, Alan
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 74)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 74a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 74b)
    - Diamond, Buzz
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 74)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 74a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 74b)
    - Kahn, Jack-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 74)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 74a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 74b)
    - Kolb, John
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 74)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 74a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 74b)
    - MacKenzie, David
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 74)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 74a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 74b)
    - Opsahl, Bill-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 74)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 74a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 74b)
    - Phelan, Howard
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 74)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 74a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 74b)
  - 1992 November 14-1992 November 21
    - Begien, Julien
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 75)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 75a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 75b)
    - Daniels, Doug-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 75)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 75a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 75b)
    - Kahn, Jack-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 75)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 75a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 75b)
    - Lindskog, Carl-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 75)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 75a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 75b)
    - Schiavone, Joel-Third interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 75)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 75a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 75b)
  - 1992 November 21
    - Harlow, Harry
      - Copy 1 of 4 (Box 76)
      - Copy 2 of 4 (Box 76a)
      - Copy 3 of 4 (Box 76b)
      - Copy 4 of 4 (Box 76c)
    - Truslow, William
      - Copy 1 of 4 (Box 76)
      - Copy 2 of 4 (Box 76a)
      - Copy 3 of 4 (Box 76b)
      - Copy 4 of 4 (Box 76c)
    - Williams, Fred
      - Copy 1 of 4 (Box 76)
      - Copy 2 of 4 (Box 76a)
      - Copy 3 of 4 (Box 76b)
      - Copy 4 of 4 (Box 76c)
    - Young, Jerry
      - Copy 1 of 4 (Box 76)
      - Copy 2 of 4 (Box 76a)
      - Copy 3 of 4 (Box 76b)
      - Copy 4 of 4 (Box 76c)
  - 1992 November 21-1992 November 22
    - Armstrong, Chris
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 77)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 77a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 77b)
    - Becklean, Bill
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 77)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 77a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 77b)
    - Stubbs, Bob
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 77)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 77a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 77b)
  - 1992 November 21-1992 December 2
    - Greenway, David
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 78)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 78a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 78b)
    - Sauer, David
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 78)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 78a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 78b)
    - Truslow, Bob
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 78)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 78a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 78b)
  - 1992 November 24
    - Cavett, Dick
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 79)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 79a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 79b)
  - 1993 January 16
    - Kwei, Tom-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 80)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 80a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 80b)
    - Kwei, Randy
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 80)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 80a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 80b)
    - Lindskog, Carl-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 80)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 80a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 80b)
    - Lindskog, David-Second interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 80)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 80a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 80b)
  - 1993 January 27 and 1993 May 1
    - Embersits, Jack and Lucinda
      - Copy 1 of 4 (Box 81)
      - Copy 2 of 4 (Box 81a)
      - Copy 3 of 4 (Box 81b)
      - Copy 4 of 4 (Box 81c)
    - Ferrante, John
      - Copy 1 of 4 (Box 81)
      - Copy 2 of 4 (Box 81a)
      - Copy 3 of 4 (Box 81b)
      - Copy 4 of 4 (Box 81c)
    - Hannah, Paul
      - Copy 1 of 4 (Box 81)
      - Copy 2 of 4 (Box 81a)
      - Copy 3 of 4 (Box 81b)
      - Copy 4 of 4 (Box 81c)
  - 1993 February 2
    - Hockaday, Peter S. (Box 83)
  - 1993 May
    - Cassell, John (Box 84)
  - 1993 May 13 and 1993 June 19
    - Cavett, Dick
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 82)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 82a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 82b)
    - Duchin, Peter-First interview
      - Copy 1 of 3 (Box 82)
      - Copy 2 of 3 (Box 82a)
      - Copy 3 of 3 (Box 82b)
- "58 Men" feature documentary on the Yale Class of 1958 [Video recordings], 1992, 2009; Accession 2018-A-037
  Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
  Scope and Contents
  The materials in this collection were created as part of the feature length documentary, "58 Men" produced in 1993 for the Yale Class of 1958's 35th reunion. The roughly 350 interviews with classmates were conducted by filmmakers Steve Bergman, MMPM '92 and John Boulet, MMPM '92 across the United States and Paris, France. The documentary is narrated by Dick Cavett '58, written by C.D.B. Bryan '58, and produced by Joel Schiavone '58 and Jack Embersits '58.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  These materials were donated by Steven Bergman, MBA'92 in 1993.
  - "58 Men" original 1" master tape, 2009
  - Original camera masters of interviews
    - #101 master-New Haven alums, 1992 May 31 (Box 2)
    - #102 master-Bill Dent (20 mins), Thomas Bauer, Peter Hunt, Bob Lontz, John Goller, Bob Strahan and Harold Hertzfeld, Undated (Box 3)
    - #103 master-Dwight Underhill, Bill Martin, Jon Jaspan, Ralph Birdsey, Bill Stack and John Payne, Undated (Box 4)
    - #104 master-Mary Ellen Payne, Fred Kreimer, David Kudzma, Tom Schlosser, Nick Kindred, Undated (Box 5)